<?xml version='1.0' standalone='yes'?>
<posts>
    <post>
        <title>About the Future of pBlog</title>
        <pubdate>29th March 2015</pubdate>
        <content>
I figured out that there will be many changes in the engine which will require many changes in the files (especially the posts file) and in the filestructure. I can't say right now which things will change and what you have to change. Out of this reason I change the Version numbers and add an zero in front of them. So instead of 2.1 the latest version is now 0.2.1. The 0.2.x series is now on GitHub as an own branch and will recive bugfix updates. The series 0.3, 0.4, 0.5 and so own will be development releases which won't be compatible to the 0.2 series. I recommend current users to stay on 0.2.x - at least until the 1.0 release. I'm verry sorry for this and in case that there are requests I may write a small script that will help you switch to version 1.0.
        </content>
    </post>
    <post>
        <title>Version 2.1</title>
        <pubdate>29th March 2015</pubdate>
        <content>This version includes fixes for the article links. You only have to replace the hrefgenerator.php file in the res folder.</content>
    </post>
    <post>
        <title>Version 2.0</title>
        <pubdate>27th March 2015</pubdate>
        <content>
This version introduces some very imporant features:
 - **Own page for every article**
 - Social **sharing buttons** (at the moment: google+, twitter, facebook but more will follow)
 - **Disqus** integration
 - Local **config file** -> no more editing the index file

pBlog 2.0 is only partially compatible with prior versions. You don't have to change anything in the posts or intro file (in case you have one), but to switch to version 2.0 you have to replace your index.php with the new one. With this step all your settings like the title will be lost and you have to set them in the new config.php file. For more questions write me a mail to marcelmichaelkapfer@yahoo.co.nz.

In the near future I will spend more time in writing a documentation about the blog engine and adding more comments (especially in the css file).
        </content>
        <mainurl>http://github.com/mmk2410/pBlog</mainurl>
        <mainlink>GitHub</mainlink>
    </post>
    <post>
        <title>Version 1.2</title>
        <pubdate>8th March 2015</pubdate>
        <content>
In this Version code is better designed so you can read and recognise it better.

This is a code example:

``scp -r * marcel-kapfer.de:``
        </content>
    </post>
    <post>
        <title>Version 1.1</title>
        <pubdate>24th February 2015</pubdate>
        <content>
After I published the Version 1.0 last sunday I realized some problems with german umlauts. Now I added a function that converts every umlaut (ü, Ü, ä, Ä, ö, Ö and ß) into the html code.
        </content>
    </post>
    <post>
        <title>Version 1.0</title>
        <pubdate>22nd February 2015</pubdate>
        <content>
Today I'm proud to announce the **Version 1.0** of the pBlog - a simple PHP, XML and Markdown based blogging engine
which is completly independent from any databases. Even if this is the version 1.0 it is still in a early state of
development.

Version 1.0 has the following features:
 - Blog writing in XML
 - Content in Markdown
 - Static intro in Markdown
        </content>
    </post>
    <post>
        <title>Version 0.3</title>
        <pubdate>20th February 2015</pubdate>
        <content>This is the Version *0.3* of pBlog. It comes with the following changes:
- Complete Markdown Support
- Design fixes
- a mainlink is no longer required
        </content>
    </post>
    <post>
	   <title>Version 0.2</title>
	   <pubdate>20th February 2015</pubdate>
	   <content>
The following things are new in this version:
- Design
- Better structur
- cleaned up

More will come when it is ready!
This is the version *0.2*.
        </content>
        <mainurl>index.php</mainurl>
		<mainlink>Reload</mainlink>
	<otherlinks>
		<otherlb>
			<otherurl>http://marcel-kapfer.de</otherurl>
			<otherlink>marcel-kapfer.de</otherlink>
        </otherlb>
        <otherlb>
			<otherurl>https://github.com/mmk2410/pblog</otherurl>
			<otherlink>GitHub</otherlink>
		</otherlb>
    </otherlinks>
    </post>
    <post>
	   <title>Blog (Experimental)</title>
	   <pubdate>13th February 2015</pubdate>
	   <content>
This is a test version in a early state of the new **blog engine**. By now it supports following things:
- Markdown
- Mainlink and various other links

More will come when it is ready!
This is the version *0.1*.
        </content>
        <mainurl>index.php</mainurl>
		<mainlink>Reload</mainlink>
	<otherlinks>
		<otherlb>
			<otherurl>http://marcel-kapfer.de</otherurl>
			<otherlink>marcel-kapfer.de</otherlink>
        </otherlb>
        <otherlb>
			<otherurl>https://github.com</otherurl>
			<otherlink>GitHub</otherlink>
		</otherlb>
    </otherlinks>
    </post>

</posts>
